AMALAMOL **RAJU**

3 Davies Close, Kettering, Northamptonshire, NN157RE

07800534808 📞

araju5500@gmail.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/am in alamol-raju-1a387b158/

https://araju55.github.io/



PERSONAL PROFILE

A passionate, hard-working second year Computer Science undergraduate with in depth knowledge gained in technical programming languages like Python, HTML, CSS, Java, etc. Strong communicator with proven experience of working within high demand restaurant dealing with customers from various backgrounds both local and international. Possessing excellent client facing skills, problem solving and identification for opportunities of improvement. Strong team player and able to deliver results for team and individual tasks. Looking for a one-year placement in a company from May to develop my skills.



EDUCATION

BSc (Hons) Computer Science | Oxford Brookes University

2017 - 2021

MODULES COMPLETED:

- Understanding Programming (Double Python)
- Foundations of Computer Systems
- Networking and Multi-media
- Introduction to Object Oriented Programming (Java)
- Professional Software System Design
- Software Development Environments
- Discrete Mathematics

CURRENT MODULES:

- Foundations of Security
- Software Development with C & C++
- Data Structure and Algorithms
- Innovative Product Development (double)
- Databases
- Foundations of Computation
- Web Application Development

A-LEVELS and GCSE's | Kettering Science Academy

2012 - 2017

- A-LEVELS: Cambridge Technicals (Distinction*), Applied Business (C) and Product Design (D)
- GCSE's: 9 B-E grades including Mathematics and English



EXPERIENCE

Team Member Star | Pret A Manger – Bicester Village, Bicester, OxfordshireOCTOBER 2017 – PRESENT

Key team member of large restaurant within a designer outlet. High demand store with constant flow of customers both local and international.

Main Responsibilities:

- Actively greeting customers and maintaining consistent levels of communication and service across the restaurant
- Taking decisive actions to improve customer services and restaurant experience
- Dealing with customer queries, complaints and orders on a regular basis
- Maintaining clean and visual standards across the store
- Operating tills
- Assisting barista and customers



Work Experience Student | Northampton College, Northampton Saints Rugby Club, Northampton, Northamptonshire

JULY 2014 - JULY 2014

• One day event where I changed the controls for a game like the background colour, game layout, formatting, etc.

TECHNICAL / KEY SKILLS

SKILLS	WHERE USED	LEVEL OF COMPETENCE
C, C++	University module assignment	Beginner
Java	University module assignment	Advanced
Python	University module exercises	Intermediate
HTML, CSS	Designed my own personal portfolio and as	Advanced
	part of my A-level assignment projects	
Microsoft Word	Constant use for university assignments	Advanced
Microsoft Access	As part of my A-level assignment projects	Advanced
Microsoft Excel	As part of my A-level assignment projects	Advanced
Microsoft Publisher	As part of my A-level assignment projects	Advanced

Communication

- Experience of liaising with younger students and teachers in my role as a Prefect at Kettering
 Science Academy. Found different ways of explaining things to help Year 9 students with their
 Mathematics homework. Communicating with other student council members as part of my role
 as a student council member to discuss possible solutions that will help improve the academy life.
- Presented project work both individually and as part of a team during my Applied Business and Cambridge Technicals A-Level. This involved preparing PowerPoint slides, delivering a presentation to a varied audience, making websites, creating databases and producing a written report.
- Experience of communicating with customers and the barista in my role as a Team Member Star
 at Pret A Manger to order the customer's drinks, taking customer's orders and dealing with the
 queries that the customers might have.

Teamwork

• Plays Cricket, helping and supporting the team to do their best by encouraging others. Regularly attends training sessions to help with the coaching of the junior team.

Responsibility

- Running Youth Groups in churches, actively involved in Sunday School.
- Teaching young children stories from the bible.
- Experience of cleaning and closing display counters ready for the next day.

Project Management

Managed projects for my team as part of my A-Level Product Design course in order to make sure
that the final product meets the requirements of the user/client. Analysed measurements using

ergonomics and anthropometrics to meet the requirements. This resulted in the user/client being happy with the product.

Organisation

• Managed my time at university to meet multiple coursework deadlines whilst working as a parttime Team Member Star at Pret A Manger in Bicester Village.

Problem-Solving

Dealing with problems in a calm and professional manner during very busy shop times. This
involved me staying calm and trying to re-solve customer problems or queries in an attentive
manner while working under pressure to reduce the queueing timings to maintain customer
satisfaction.



ACCOMPLISHMENTS

- Awarded Video Game Programming Basic Level by Computer Xplorers SE Wales in October 2008.
- Awarded a Bronze award for 3rd place in the Bee-Bot Olympics by Computer Xplorers SE Wales in July 2008.
- Awarded CSI with Computer Microscopes and Bee-Bot Olympics by Computer Xplorers SE Wales in July 2008.



INTERESTS

- Enjoy playing and watching football as well as playing badminton.
- Play the keyboard.



REFERENCES

AVAILABLE UPON REQUEST